# MARÍA LAURA RUSSO FELIZAR



(+5411) 6787-2803



in www.linkedin.com/in/lrfelizar



✓ Irfelizar@gmail.com



github.com/Irfelizar



C.U.I.L.: 27-36399296-5



Irfelizar.github.io/laurarusso.git hub.io/#home



Dr. Luis Belaustegui 1849 CABA (1416)

Student of Higher Technician in Programming at Teclab Institute (2nd and last year).

I am a proactive, organized and responsible person.

With my work experience, I have become and independent and efficient person, able to diagram informatics solutions in a fast and effective way.

Nowadays, I am expanding my abilities in Front End area, learning languages such as Javascript, also frameworks and libraries.

I am in the search of new challenges that give me the chance to grow as a professional.

# SKILLS

• English: Advanced • Portuguese: Basic

Microsoft Office: Advanced

· Corel Draw: Advanced

· Adobe: Illustrator, Photoshop, XD (Medium knowledge)

 Programming skills: HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, Jquery.js, Bootstrap 4, Github, Wordpress. Also learning React.

# EDUCATION

#### **Teclab Institute**

HIGHER TECHNICIAN IN PROGRAMMING 2019 - PRESENT

## Coderhouse

UX DESIGN 2018

# IFTS N° 20: "Héroes de Malvinas"

HIGHER TECHNICIAN IN HOTEL MANAGEMENT - 2019

## Monseñor Dillon School

ACCOUNTING TAX ASSISTANT - 2009

# EXPERIENCES

## **Professional Practice**

INFORMATIC'S MUSEUM OCTOBER - DECEMBER (2019)

• Wordpress web page managment and Content creation for facebook and instagram with Adobe Photoshop.

# Free-lance

ARTIST - WEB DESIGN (2019)

- Web design with wordpress template for spanish artist, including all the content displayed at the site, such as logos.
- https://www.jordancer.com

## Co-owner

FETUCCI PIZZA PARTY (DECEMBER 2018 - PRESENT)

## Store Manager

RESTAURANT "EL SICILIANO" (DECEMBER 2018 - MARCH 2020)

## **Store Manager**

ALFA GRÁFICA DIGITAL (DECEMBER 2015 - OCTOBER 2018)

• Customer support, Corel Draw design work for billing, personal cards and any graphic design needed.